Downloaded @ subs4free.club
You're a great dancer.
I'm amazing.
Take it easy, I guess.
You sure you don't
want to say anything?
I'd say fuck too many times.
She wouldn't care.
No.
Oh, come on.
I can't believe he came.
Both Maya and I appreciate all
of you taking the time
to help us say goodbye
to our mother, Laura Welch.
Mom lived her life as a nurse,
caring for others as
if they were her own children.
Hey.
Like a good Buddhist,
she always said,
"Happiness never decreases
by being shared."
Few of us
could follow her noble example.
But as most of you know,
my sister Maya came close,
spending the last nine months
caring for her around the clock.
She's been a blessing
in this hellish year,
and for that I thank her.
Yeah. This sucks.
She would have hated this.
Hey, girls.
Doug. How are you?
It's good to see you,
Mr. Welch.
This must be Cleo. Hey, Cleo.
- Here, let me take her.
- Where'd you fly in from?
London.
I just wish I'd come sooner.
I should have been here for you.
You haven't been here for us
in a long time.
I was an idiot, and I blew it,
and I wish I could
take it all back.
But right now,
I just want to try
and make it up to you two,
please.
Maya. Hey.
What are you gonna do now?
- Going home.
- I mean for work.
Look, maybe this is
the last thing
you want to talk about
right now,
but I might have something
for you,
if you're interested.
I don't know the first thing
about real estate.
Oh, you don't need to.
All you need is to be charming.
And under that tough exterior,
I know you are.
Foreign buyers,
mostly from Egypt and India.
Young.
When they come
and look at the property,
they want someone to squire them
around the city for a few days.
-Coddle them.
-Like an escort.
Like an agent.
You know,
someone cool they can relate to.
Young, alive and fun.
Well, I'm one of those things.
A thousand dollars a day,
three weeks minimum.
We'll see after that.
What's the catch?
There's no catch.
But you have to meet them
first in Cairo for a few days,
and then bring them here.
I haven't seen you in years.
I don't even know you.
Oh, come on, Maya.
You know me.
We were a good team.
It was always you and me.
But you're right.
It's been too long, and
it's my fault, so let me fix it.
You've had a brutal year.
You've just lost your mother.
Let me...
Let me be your father.
I can't believe I'm gonna
have to pack
up this place all by myself.
What do you think?
I think this is crazy.
-I know.
-No. This is crazy.
Let me see your eyes.
I'm not wasted. What the fuck?
I don't know.
He just comes along, and
you're just gonna go with him.
I thought you were trying
to get control of your life.
It's work. Okay?
He still owes us for
the funeral, the hospital bed.
Paid. He wired us the money.
Everything's taken care of.
Everything? I doubt that.
See? Sam Welch.
Sent yesterday.
He's doing what
he's supposed to.
Just give him a break.
From a bank
in South Korea.
Well, he is
Mr. International Businessman.
I wouldn't go with him
no matter how much he paid.
He's the only parent
I have left.
And come on, Jess.
I spent the last nine months
stuck in this apartment
watching Mom die.
I'll do anything,
go anywhere
to get out of this place.
- Hey.
- Hey, you made it.
I have something for you.
A week up front,
as you requested.
You were always
a tough negotiator
since the day you were born.
What was I negotiating for?
Love?
You know what you want,
and you know how to get it.
So not love.
You're willing to take risks.
You get things done.
That's something we both share.
You know, you've never said
anything like that to me before.
Ms. Welch,
would you like
anything else before we depart?
- I'm fine, thanks.
- Mr. Robertson?
No, not for me.
Thank you.
Robertson?
She must be tired.
To new ventures.
It's a 42 floor glass tower,
three story lobby,
two pools, rooftop, basement.
Who's buying it?
Consortium
of wealthy individuals.
One's in telecom, another owns
a car company in India.
So you help
rich people launder their money.
Uh, no.
Well, isn't that what high end
New York real estate's
all about?
- That's not who my clients are.
- How do you know?
Because if they were,
I'd be making a lot more money.
Excuse me.
-Sam!
-Khalil!
-How you doing?
-Good, my friend.
-Good to see you.
-Welcome back.
Thank you. Wow. What?
Is that the cheapest cigar
you could find?
You know me, Sam.
I don't like cigars.
So this is she.
Maya, this is Khalil Ibrahim,
business partner and friend.
-For Miss Maya,
small beauty for great beauty.
Thank you.
Welcome to Egypt.
There you are.
-Hey.
Look what I found.
- Oh, my God.
- You were what, 6?
Remember that trip?
-Yeah?
-Barely.
You looked like your mom
even then.
Nah, everyone says
I look like you.
We were like two peas in a
pod, making trouble, having fun.
They stood right here,
put their hands here,
laid these massive stones
into place.
They were slaves, right?
No one knows their names
or anything about them.
We barely even remember
the kings.
Ever heard of Rahotep,
Intef, Thutmose?
- No.
- How about Hatshepsut,
longest reigning female pharaoh?
She was a good ruler
in hard times.
Akhenaten was ineffectual.
Seti was brutal.
They all thought their
little dramas were important,
but in the end,
they're just specks of sand.
Same as the guys
who laid these stones.
Insignificant.
That's depressing.
Or freeing.
You ready to go?
Sure.
Tell me about Robertson.
What?
I saw your Robertson passport
on the plane.
My nom de plume.
You're not a writer.
Don't lie to me.
The least you can do
is tell me the truth.
I sell real estate.
I do. But in the past,
you know, my clients were
sometimes a little sketchy.
It was easier to use
a different name,
so it wouldn't get back to
your mom or you kids.
How were they sketchy?
Some were fighting wars,
which made them desperate,
sometimes dangerous.
-What do you do for them?
-Did. Not anymore.
Okay, what did you do?
I laundered their money
through real estate.
Of course.
Where'd that money go?
To buy information or influence.
Or weapons?
In some cases, yes.
So, dictators, terrorists?
No. No. I backed the Kurds in
Syria, LGBT activists in Russia.
I helped fund the Arab Spring.
You know, that certainly pissed
off a few people here in Egypt,
But I choose my clients as much
as they choose me.
Anyway, that's all in the past,
you know?
And I'm just stuck
with Robertson.
What did you do
when we lived in Turkey?
Worked for
the State Department.
Doing what?
Connecting with locals,
gathering information.
You were a spy.
Did mom know?
Of course she knew.
Is that why we went home?
No, I...
She was just tired of moving
every few years.
Didn't want to bring
two children up that way,
and she was right.
I don't miss her.
Oh, Maya,
it's too soon, you know?
The reality hasn't hit you yet.
She really was a saint.
There was no one
she wouldn't try to help.
I wanted to be like her, but...
I'm not.
You know, it's kind of hard
to say out loud,
but I was relieved
when I left the hospital.
I felt almost giddy.
Freedom.
Then the guilt hit me,
like a shovel to the skull.
All of that is normal.
You know that, right?
I don't know.
I just need to move on.
Let me help you move on.
Look, none of this
is important or world-changing,
but I've built something here.
Something real.
And I want you and I
to run it together.
Sorry, hold on.
I got to take this.
Don't move.
Okay? What?
Uh, can I get
another one of these?
Yes, ma'am.
What's up?
Maya, leave the
restaurant. Now.
Why? I just ordered.
Now! I'll take care of
the bill later.
Just get my iPad
and walk away fast.
Okay, you're freaking me out.
What is going on?
Just hurry up.
- I'm going.
- Don't hang up.
Let me know
when you're at the door.
You're being weird.
Just go.
Okay, I'm out.
Where are you?
Walk away
from the restaurant.
- The cops are here.
- Just keep moving.
Go.
He's inside?
And you confirmed?
-Yes. Yeah.
-Did you?
Yes.
He's inside. Ready to go.
Copy that.
- What is going on?
- You have my iPad?
Yes.
Head away from the river.
Okay, but where are you?
What the fuck is going on?
I'll meet you
at the Zebdya Cafe.
The Zebdya Cafe.
It's south of you.
Just take a left at the next
street and walk three blocks.
You understand?
No, Dad, I don't.
I don't. What the fuck?
I'll see you there.
We're sorry.
You have reached a number
that has been disconnected
or is no longer in --
-Miss Maya.
-Where's my dad?
Please, he...
Something happened to him.
-What do you mean?
-Have a seat.
Two men,
they pushed him into a van.
No, I was just on the phone
with him.
- He's coming here.
- Saw it myself.
He knew they were
looking for him.
I was rushing to get there,
but I was too late.
There were police
at the restaurant.
I thought that's why he left.
What color uniform?
Green or white?
Or dark blue?
-Not white, darker.
-We must go now.
- To the hotel?
- We can't go back there.
Why not?
Please, Miss Maya, your father
asked me to keep you safe.
I must do that. Let's go.
Why aren't we calling
the police?
It's not that simple.
There are good police
and bad police, like everywhere.
This is not New York.
You have to know who to talk to.
It might be the police
who kidnapped him.
Why would
the police kidnap him?
He made some enemies
here during the Arab Spring.
Let me make some phone calls,
and I will find out.
Who's that?
Answer it.
- Hello.
- Maya Welch?
Who is this?
- Hello?
- Maya, it's me.
Dad? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just so sorry this
is happening.
Please don't worry.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Wait. What is going on?
What happened?
Look, I know I told you
I was done with that old life,
but I'm sorry.
It's just business.
They want something I have.
Something they paid for.
I need you to get it for me.
Okay, well, what do I do?
You have my iPad?
Open it to the calendar.
Okay, I don't have
your password.
It's your birthday,
sweetheart.
There's an appointment
tomorrow morning.
Uh...
Okay, I see it.
Good.
Just go there,
tell them my name.
They'll give you something.
And then...
And then where do I bring it?
It's not that simple.
You got to make another stop.
You'll see.
Don't talk to anyone about this.
No one.
Okay.
And don't tell
Khalil, okay?
And destroy the iPad,
smash it, throw it in the trash.
Give me the phone.
No more.
Maya Welch, if you go to
the police, he's dead.
If you don't bring it to us,
you are dead.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- You have two days.
Jesus Christ.
What did he tell you?
He, uh...
He wants me to get something
so they'll release him.
What it is? Where?
He doesn't want me
to tell anyone.
- Even me?
- I don't know.
I guess not.
Look, I have to go to the hotel.
That is a bad idea.
Okay, well...
What about if you go?
Please, it's just --
it's one bag.
My computer's in it,
and, you know,
some female stuff.
Don't let anyone in.
And keep the door locked
behind me.
United States Embassy.
This is the emergency number.
What's your emergency?
I, uh -- I think my dad's
been kidnapped.
Are you
an American citizen?
- Yes.
- The duty office is
not available right now,
but we'll call you back
at this number.
Are you in a safe place?
-I mean, I think so, but I...
Can I come there?
Can I come to the Embassy?
We don't open
until 7:00.
Maya.
Do you hate your father
so much you want him to die?
Why is it so hard to help him?
Your family is not my business,
but I'm very fond of Sam.
He has helped me many times.
I saw a woman go inside.
She was with the police
at the restaurant last night.
And what
does that tell you?
I don't know.
I don't think you are
really that naive.
Look, if you don't want
help him, just let me.
I will do what needs to be done.
Just tell me what it is.
He wants me to do it.
I'll do it.
Thanks.
Hi.
I'm here to pick up something
for Sam Welch.
No.
I was told that you have
something for Sam Welch.
I need it.
Do you want to buy something?
No. I...
What about Sam Robertson?
Who?
Sam Robertson.
I'm his daughter.
This?
What did you expect,
Miss Robertson?
Holy shit. Okay.
This is what you've got to do.
You've got to go to the airport
and get on the first plane home.
What? I can't just leave.
Of course you can.
If he has gotten himself
into trouble,
it is not your job
to get him out of it.
But I can get him out
of it, okay?
He just needs me
to get him something.
What? A ransom?
Come on, Maya.
How are you supposed
to get that?
It's in India.
I have to go there.
That's crazy.
Do not go to India.
You are not up for this.
What's that supposed to mean?
Maya, just
get out of there, okay?
Go straight to the airport
right now!
650.
Thanks.
Passport, please.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please make sure
that your seat belt is fastened
and that your seat is
in the upright position.
In a few minutes,
we will be landing in Delhi.
57,500.
Hello? This hotel good.
Come.
Here.
- You want my...?
- Please come.
-Here.
-How much?
1,500.
- Excuse me?
- Yes.
Good morning, ma'am.
Hi. I'd like to access
my safe deposit box.
Okay.
Have you got the papers?
I have the key, as well.
Yes, I'll ask for that later.
This way.
Please watch your step, ma'am.
Keys.
In case if you need anything
else, I'm just right on outside.
- You have it?
- Yes.
Tomorrow, you will go to
Chandni Chowk Market,
to Esplande Road.
In Cairo?
In Delhi.
You will walk the length
of the road.
Someone will meet you.
And I give it to them?
Tomorrow morning, 10:00.
We'll be watching to see
that you are alone.
Where's my father?
This is the way
that we'll do it.
No. No.
I'll bring this back to Cairo,
and I'll give it to you
when I see him.
He's not in Cairo.
Then where is he?
Do what we say,
or he dies.
Fuck you.
You prove to me he's safe,
or I don't give you shit.
New York.
-What?
-You're from New York.
-Maybe.
-It's written all over you.
-Is it?
-I was there two weeks ago,
visiting my brother.
He's a capitalist.
He moves capital.
What about you?
Thought it was written
all over me.
Artist.
No.
Punk rocker.
Wow.
That's crazy.
- You're in a band.
- We're here on tour.
I knew it.
When can I see you play?
- You missed us.
- Did I?
-Last night was it.
- Where was the show?
- I have no idea.
What are you doing now?
I'm meeting some friends.
One of them's a musician, too.
At a place just around
the corner.
Come with me.
They're good people.
I have to get up early.
That doesn't sound
very rock and roll.
Just one drink.
I can't.
You're not really
in a band, are you?
Actually, I am.
No, you're not.
You're a spy.
Wait. Are you a spy?
Of course.
You gave that
away pretty easy.
You must be new.
Yeah. Yeah, brand new.
CIA? Who are you spying on?
I'll never tell.
You can trust me.
I can help you.
Oh, okay.
This is getting too weird.
Come on. I'm just teasing.
Excuse me?
Could I get the check?
- Right away.
- Hey, I am just teasing.
All right?
Let me buy you a drink.
Fuck.
Come with me.
I'll have what you want.
Maya Welch, look ahead.
Keep walking.
I'm not giving you anything
until I see my dad.
-Keep moving. Okay.
Walk, walk.
I'm going.
Answer it.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm fine. You can hand it over.
Where are you?
I'm walking away from them now.
- They could grab you again.
- They won't.
They won't if you --
if you give it to them now.
Okay?
Shit!
What? What?
Maya, what's going on?
Maya!
Hey!
Hello?
- What happened?
- There were police.
They got your man.
Do you still
have the drive?
Yes, but I need to know where --
Listen carefully.
Go straight to
the train station.
Do not go back to any hotel.
Take the 1310 train to Mumbai,
Central Terminal.
Someone will meet you there.
Where's my dad?
Write down the number,
then throw away your phone,
or the police will track you.
Where is my dad?
Tell me.
Hey. Hey, are you a taxi?
Yeah, of course.
Where can I take you,
young lady?
Train station.
Can you take this turn?
Of course, ma'am.
Are they looking for you, ma'am?
It's my ex-boyfriend.
He'll kill me if he finds me.
Kill you?
Okay.
Shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, whoa!
Police! Stop!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, now, go!
Ticket counter is there.
He's dangerous?
I mean your ex.
Yes, he is.
Looks like he bought
half the police force.
They are all a bunch of crooks.
Here.
No, no, this is too much money.
Please. You saved me.
I didn't mean that -- I mean...
Take it. Thank you.
-Train to Mumbai.
-Mumbai?
Mumbai.
May I have
your attention...
Do you mind?
No, of course not.
This country, eh?
I'm Emily.
Carol.
Nice to meet you, Carol.
You had a good sleep.
-Jet lag.
-Tell me about it.
Going all the way to Mumbai?
Yeah. You?
Yeah. Just in Delhi for the
weekend visiting my boyfriend.
We work for
Arms Around the World.
Missionaries?
They thump the bible
back at headquarters,
but out here,
we just want to get people fed.
But you're a believer.
In making a difference
in people's lives?
Yeah. Otherwise,
why am I taking up space?
You don't worry about fucking
things up even more?
Yeah.
But what else
are we going to do?
Stick our heads in the sand?
There's too many people.
There's too much suffering.
What's the point?
And yet, maybe when we save
someone else, we save ourselves.
My mom used to say that.
-Yeah?
You should listen to her.
Smart woman.
- Hello?
- Maya Welch.
My name is Erika Papp.
I work for Interpol.
-Interpol?
We know you're in Delhi.
I saw you myself.
And I need you to come
to the US Embassy right away.
You understand?
-I can't do that.
-You're in possession of
stolen US government property.
Classified material.
This is serious.
But bring us what you have,
and I'll make sure you
don't get into any trouble.
Maybe you don't realize who
your father's mixed up with.
Who's he mixed up with?
North Korea, for one.
They're looking for him,
and for you.
Do you know
where your father is right now?
My father was kidnapped.
Kidnapped? No. He left
Egypt on a private plane.
We were expecting him in India
and planned to arrest him
at the border,
but he must have found that out.
So instead, he sent you.
You didn't know that, did you?
I have to go.
You can't leave India.
You can't get to your father.
Maya...
You okay?
What is it?
It's my dad.
Oh, no. Is he okay?
Uh...
I don't know. I just found out
that he's been lying to me.
Families, right?
I suppose the only thing you
can do is talk to your father.
Give him a chance
to explain himself.
Yeah.
But I don't even know
where he is.
Will you watch my stuff?
-Careful! Excuse me.
Ma'am,
what are you doing?
-That's eight. Okay.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Hi.
Is Seoul your final
destination, Ms. Fergus?
Yes, it is.
Thanks.
Go.
Fortunas flight 393 with
service to Incheon, South Korea.
Mask down.
Hi.
Uh, do you sell phones?
Like a mobile phone?
Do you sell them here?
Yes.
Please leave a card.
Hey, hey.
-Hi, Daddy.
-Hi. How are you?
Hey. Hello, honey girl.
How are you?
You good?
-Good.
Did you get me
something nice?
-Yeah!
-What did you get me?
Did you get me some toys?
-We got your favorite stuff.
-Wow. Let's see.
Do you have a reservation?
No.
- Who is this?
- I need to talk to my father.
You didn't show up in
Mumbai. Where are you?
Put him on the phone,
or I'm going to the US Embassy.
Interpol already contacted me.
You still have
the hard drive?
Put my father on.
He's not here.
Well, find him.
Now, or I'm gone.
Are you there?
Hold.
Maya, you okay?
You safe?
I'm fine.
I was so worried when
they said you didn't show up.
Thank God you're all right.
I'm so sorry.
This was too much to ask of you.
Yeah.
Do you have it?
What they want?
I do.
I'm ready to make a trade.
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
That's why I came to
Seoul, to give it to you.
To Seoul?
Yeah.
Dad?
I knew you were smart.
No. No, I'm stupid.
Very stupid.
Where are you exactly?
Aren't you
going to say it?
You weren't kidnapped.
It was the only way.
I couldn't go to India.
Then the police showed up.
I had to get out of there.
Why didn't you
just tell me?
I couldn't take
the chance you'd say no,
so I did what I had to do.
Otherwise, I was a dead man.
I'm sorry. You're the only one
I could trust.
Trust?
Don't you mean manipulate?
-I mean the only one
strong enough, smart enough,
fearless enough to...
...to get the job done.
What's on
the hard drive, Dad?
Are you working
for Interpol now?
Fuck you.
Maya, don't move.
Don't move. You think I wanted
to put you through all this?
I had no choice.
I was hired to do a job,
and now I have to deliver.
Who are they?
It doesn't matter.
Just give it to me, okay?
I'm running out of time here.
Maya?
Ma--
Hey. How are you?
-Good.
-You good?
-Are you okay?
-I'm good. I'm good.
This too.
Okay.
Thanks.
- Hello?
- Maya.
I know I fucked up, really.
But I need this.
How's your family?
Look, I'm not perfect.
I've lied a lot.
But this, Maya, is the truth.
If I don't get that drive,
I am a dead man.
This is big, Maya.
Bigger than I ever planned.
My fee,
it's enough for both of us.
You can retire on it.
Never work again,
starting tomorrow.
I know you didn't inherit
anything from your mother,
so at least take this.
It's what you're entitled to.
Everything I've never given you,
but now I can.
Maya?
I know you hate me,
but you don't hate me
enough to kill me.
Maya?
Okay, Dad.
Hangang Bridge, one hour.
Maya?
I'm so incredibly sorry.
But I'm grateful, too.
You really didn't have to come
through with this, but you did.
So thank you.
I know you can never forgive me,
and you shouldn't,
but at least take the money.
I know it's not going
to make up for what I've done,
but it'll ease the pain.
-You know, this bridge
during the Korean War,
when the North was invading
and the South was retreating,
this was the only way
to cross the river.
So they wired it with explosives
to keep the North back.
Only problem was,
they didn't warn the
South Korean refugees fleeing.
So when the bridge exploded,
over 1,000 people were killed.
And that's horrible,
but it was a war, you know?
Maybe it saved a lot more lives.
Maybe it was worth it,
for the greater good.
Is that what you're working for?
The greater good?
I'm working for the good
of my family.
I want to make sure we win,
that you win.
That I win?
Right.
I can't do this twice, Maya.
I can't live my life again
and see if different decisions
would change this moment.
We're stuck with
what we've done,
and guilt is as useless
as those prayers
your mom used to say
to her Buddha.
It changes nothing.
And she was no saint.
Everything Laura did
was for praise.
Her generosity,
just a way of getting
what she wanted from the world.
Everyone acts
in their own self-interest.
Even her. Even you.
So do you have it?
Hey, come on. Maya, please.
Maya.
-Do you really think
I got on that plane with you
because of money?
We both know I came
because of you, Dad.
I wanted you.
And I was hoping that maybe...
you came to see me.
I am here for you.
Absolutely, I am.
Oh, but this...
this is why you came
to Mom's funeral, isn't it?
No. No.
Lie to me again.
Go ahead.
Okay, yes, yes.
I needed your help,
but then when I saw you,
the woman you are now,
you've become an amazing person,
an original.
That's when it stopped
being about that damn drive.
I love you, Maya.
I didn't want this to happen.
You really are my special one.
And you love me no matter what?
Of course.
Okay.
Good.
Fuck.
You stupid cunt.
Your special one, huh?
Fuck you.
Are you okay?
Should I call someone?
No. I'm fine.
- Should I call the cops?
- No cops. No cops.
Fuck.
Mask.
I'm at an airport in Seoul
about to board a flight.
You're in South Korea?
Yeah. Seoul.
He lives here.
But what happened?
Nothing.
It was all a misunderstanding.
US Customs and Border
Protection welcomes you
to the United States of America.
On your person,
please have all travel documents
out and with you.
And remember, if you see
something, say something.
Next in line.
- Hey.
- Welcome home.
Maya Welch?
Yeah.
We're gonna need you to come
with us. This way, please.
Turn around.
Anything in your pockets?
Spread your legs.
You can have a seat over here.
Can you just...
You're on, ma'am.
-Hello, Maya.
-What's your name again?
It's ma'am.
How did you manage
to get to South Korea?
The chatter around here
is that you dumped the drive
in the Han River.
Is that true?
Yeah, I was pretty pissed off
at my dad.
I suppose
I should thank you
for making sure it didn't end up
somewhere else, but I won't.
Well, you're welcome anyway.
- Where's Sam?
- Don't care.
Well, do you care
that what you did is a crime?
That drive had military secrets
on it, but also money.
Millions of dollars
in digital currency.
Apparently with the password
written right on the drive.
You should have brought it
to us, Maya.
But you're a fool,
just like your father.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Your name is on it,
but it was sent to me.
From Dad?
Something I picked up
for myself.
-Jewelry?
-Wow.
It's like you don't
even know me.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Why'd you send it to me?
That's weird.
I didn't know if I'd be back
in time to get it.
You want coffee?
You're not gonna open it?
No.
When's the broker get here?
Soon.
Is he almost done?
How much longer
do you think?
I don't know.
About 15 minutes.
Okay, cool.
What are you doing?
What the hell is this?
My inheritance.